palmresearch.com 2018-09-09

# Privacy Policy - Palm Research

Privacy Policy  
Use of our site located at http://palmresearch.com (or any variation of palmresearch.com) indicates acceptance of our Privacy Policy.  
Privacy of Information  
Palm Research believes in honest marketing and fair business practices. Because of this, we promise to never share your personal and confidential information with any party for their data collecting / advertising / promotional purposes. We will, however, share personal and confidential information with authorities if required to do so by law.  
The information we collect, including but not limited to, name, age, mailing address and phone number, is solely used for contacting you about your member account. We will never ask you to confirm your personal information through email, with the exception that, from time to time, we may ask you to log in to your account and confirm the information.  
Cookie and Pixel Tracking  
Our members participate in surveys linked to from our site, and in order to provide "real time" tracking to our members, we may utilize the cookie function of your computer browser. This cookie only stores information limited to the survey panel number and member number and can only be accessed by our site.  
Third Party Websites  
Palm Research offers surveys from our partners and other third party websites. Please refer to their respective privacy policies for information on how they handle personal information.  
Changes to our Privacy Policy  
Please check this page periodically for any changes to our privacy policy. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time.  
| Revised on April 14, 2018  
---
